BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/017
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Printers - Bay City, MI, 1923-1927 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  1923, 1924, 1927
- Printers - Taunton, MA, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Printers - Springfield, MA, 1914-1918 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Printers - Worcester, MA, 1912-1926 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  1912-1919, 1923-1926
- Printers - Omaha, NE, 1912-1927 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  1912-1914, 1918-1923, 1927
- Printers - Portsmouth, NH, 1920-1922 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  1920, 1921, 1922
- Printers - Manchester, NH, 1907-1920 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  1907, 1911, 1912, 1915-1917, 1920
- Printers - Omaha, NE, 1914-1927 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  1914-1920, 1923, 1927
- Printers - Lincoln, NE, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 68)
- Printers - Jersey City, NJ, 1902 (Box 9, Folder 69)
- Printers - Wichita, KS, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 70)
- Printers - Rochester, NY, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 71)
- Printers - Rockville Center, NY, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 72)
- Printers - Rome, NY, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 73)
- Printers - Schenectady, NY, 1910-1925 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  1910, 1913, 1924, 1925
- Printers - Syracuse, NY, 1922-1925 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  1922, 1924, 1925
- Printers - Great Falls, MT, 1921-1928 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  1921, 1928
- Printers - Missoula, MT, 1921-1927 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  1921, 1927
- Printers - Butte, MT, 1914-1923 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  1914, 1917-1920, 1923
- Printers - Hannibal, MO, 1924-1927 (Box 9, Folder 79)
- Printers - Anaconda, MT, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 80)
- Printers - Houston, TX, 1913-1920 (Box 9, Folder 81)
- Printers - St. Louis, MO, 1910-1924 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  1910, 1915, 1916, 1920, 1924
- Printers - Boston, MA, 1911-1926 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  1911, 1916-1926
- Printers - St. Joseph, MO, 1921-1928 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  1921, 1925, 1927, 1928
- Printers - St. Louis, MO, 1911-1923 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  1911, 1915-1917, 1920, 1923
- Printers - Sedalia, MO, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 86)
- Printers - Attleboro, MA, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 87)
- Printers - Memphis, TN, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 88)
- Printers - Ellensburg, WA, 1924-1926 (Box 9, Folder 89)
- Printers - Bellingham, WA, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 90)
- Printers - Richmond, VA, 1906-1925 (Box 9, Folder 91)
  1906, 1917, 1918, 1923, 1925
- Printers - Huntington, WV, 1922-1925 (Box 9, Folder 92)
- Printers - Auburn, NY, 1924-1926 (Box 9, Folder 93)
- Printers - Batavia, NY, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 94)
- Printers - Elmira, NY, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 95)
- Printers - Cohoes, NY, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 96)
- Printers - Geneva, NY, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 97)
- Printers - Glens Falls, NY, 1923-1926 (Box 9, Folder 98)
- Printers - Gloversville, NY, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 99)
- Printers - Jamestown, NY, 1923-1925 (Box 9, Folder 100)
- Printers - Middletown, NY, 1923-1926 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  1923, 1924, 1926
- Printers - Hoboken, NJ, 1924-1927 (Box 9, Folder 102)
- Printers - Oklahoma City, OK, 1923-1926 (Box 9, Folder 103)
- Printers - Muskogee, OK, 1924 (Box 9, Folder 104)
- Printers - Okmulgee, OK, 1921 (Box 9, Folder 105)
- Printers - Portland, ME, 1916-1925 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  1916, 1920, 1922, 1925
- Printers - Zanesville, OH, 1925-1927 (Box 9, Folder 107)
- Printers - East Liverpool, OH, 1921-1923 (Box 9, Folder 108)
- Printers - Hamilton, OH, 1923-1927 (Box 9, Folder 109)
- Printers - Ironton, OH, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 110)
- Printers - Lima, OH, 1925 (Box 9, Folder 111)
- Printers - Hackensack, NJ, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 112)
- Printers - Colorado Springs, CO, 1920-1926 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  1920, 1924, 1926
- Printers - Charleston, IL, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 114)
- Printers - Washington D.C., 1912-1926 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  1912, 1916, 1917, 1920-1923, 1926
- Printers - Olean, NY, 1923-1925 (Box 9, Folder 116)
- Printers - Oneida, NY, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 117)
- Printers - Oneonta, NY, 1925-1927 (Box 9, Folder 118)
- Printers - Newburgh, NY, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Printers - Niagara Falls, NY, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Printers - Lawrence, KS, 1923-1924 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Printers - Denver, CO, 1915-1923 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  1915, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1923
- Printers - Washington D.C., 1907 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Printers - Atlanta, GA, 1909-1916 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  1909, 1916
- Printers - Augusta, GA, 1926-1928 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  1926, 1927, 1928
- Printers - Chicago, IL, 1910-1923 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  1910, 1911, 1913, 1916, 1919-1923
- Printers - New Haven, CT, 1911-1921 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  1911, 1918, 1919, 1921
- Printers - New London, CT, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Printers - Waterbury, CT, 1924-1927 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Printers - Wilmington, DE, 1922-1924 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Printers - Little Rock, AR, 1911-1919 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  1911, 1914, 1919
- Printers - Belleville, IL, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Printers - Bloomington, IL, 1921-1925 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  1921, 1923, 1925
- Printers - Indianapolis, IN, 1915-1926 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  1915, 1919,-1926
- Printers - Kokomo, IN, 1925-1927 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Printers - LaFayette, IN, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Printers - Marion, IN, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Printers - St. Augustine, FL, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Printers - Athens, GA, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Printers - La Salle Peru, IL, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Printers - Kewanee, IL, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Printers - Joliet, IL, 1924-1927 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Printers - Jacksonville and Beardstown, FL, 1923-1927 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Printers - Richmond, IL, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Printers - Los Angeles, CA, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Printers - Ottawa, IL, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Printers - Washington D.C., 1912-1926 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  1912, 1918, 1919, 1924, 1926
- Printers - Peoria, IL, 1916-1923 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  1916, 1918, 1920, 1923
- Printers - Chicago, IL, 1907-1923 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  1907, 1911, 1913, 1916, 1919, 1920, 1923
- Printers - South Bend, IN, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Printers - Bakersfield, CA, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Printers - New York, NY, 1910-1920 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  1910, 1916, 1918, 1920
- Printers - Akron, OH, 1924-1926 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Printers - Denver, CO, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Printers - Washington D.C., 1911 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Printers - Los Angeles, CA, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Printers - New York, NY (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Printers - National, 1919-1923 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Printers - Buffalo, NY, 1913 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Printers - Cleveland, OH, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Printers - Philadelphia, PA, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Printers - Atlanta, GA, 1904 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Printers - Kansas City, MO, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Printers - Des Moines, IA, 1914-1927 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  1914, 1917-1927
- Printers - Dubuque, IA, 1924-1926 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Printers - Keokuk, IA, 1923-1927 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Printers - Muscatine, IA, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Printers - Ottumwa, IA, 1902-1927 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  1902, 1905, 1921, 1927
- Printers - Sioux Falls, IA, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Printers - Binghamton, NY, 1924-1927 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  1924, 1926, 1927
- Printers - Burlington, IA, 1923-1927 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Printers - Terre Haute, IN, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Printers - Washington, IN, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Printers - Los Angeles, CA, 1910-1924 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  1910-1914, 1917-1921, 1924
- Printers - San Francisco, CA, 1914-1928 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  1914, 1918-1920, 1924, 1925, 1928
- Printers - Pensacola, FL, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Printers - St. Augustine, FL, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Printers - Tampa, FL, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Printers - San Francisco, CA, 1910-1925 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  1910, 1915-1925
- Printers - Cleveland, OH, 1907-1925 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  1907, 1912, 1916-1925
- Printers - El Paso, TX, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Printers - San Antonio, TX, 1922-1923 (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Printers - Nashville, TN, 1917-1923 (Box 10, Folder 65)
  1917, 1920, 1923
- Printers - Abilene, TX, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 66)
- Printers - Dallas, TX, 1910-1917 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  1910, 1911, 1914, 1917
- Printers - Coffeyville, KS, 1924-1926 (Box 10, Folder 68)
- Printers - Girard, KS, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Printers - New York, NY, 1912-1916 (Box 10, Folder 70)
- Printers - Waterloo, IA, 1927 (Box 10, Folder 71)
- Printers - Trenton, NJ, 1924-1927 (Box 10, Folder 72)
- Printers - Raton, NM, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 73)
- Printers - Santa Fe, NM, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 74)
- Printers - Albany, NY, 1923-1925 (Box 10, Folder 75)
- Printers - Decatur, IL, 1925-1927 (Box 10, Folder 76)
- Printers - New York, NY, 1925-1926 (Box 10, Folder 77)
- Printers - Springfield, IL, 1914-1926 (Box 10, Folder 78)
  1914, 1920, 1926
- Printers - Grand Rapids, MI, 1914-1924 (Box 10, Folder 79)
- Printers - Jackson, MI, 1921-1926 (Box 10, Folder 80)
- Printers - Winnipeg, Manitoba, 1923-1927 (Box 10, Folder 81)
  1923, 1925, 1926, 1927
- Printers - Salt Lake City, UT, 1914-1924 (Box 10, Folder 82)
  1914, 1915, 1918, 1921, 1924
- Printers - Galveston, TX, 1922-1927 (Box 10, Folder 83)
- Printers - Wichita Falls, TX, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 84)
- Printers - Nashville, TN, 1915-1923 (Box 10, Folder 85)
  1915, 1921, 1923
- Printers - Amarillo, TX, 1920-1924 (Box 10, Folder 86)
- Printers - Seattle, WA, 1911-1924 (Box 10, Folder 87)
  1911-1913, 1917, 1920, 1921, 1924
- Printers - Scranton, PA, 1904-1915 (Box 10, Folder 88)
  1904, 1910, 1915
- Printers - Indianapolis, IN, 1912-1917 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  1912, 1917
- Printers - Washington D.C., 1923 (Box 10, Folder 90)
- Printers - Ft. Lauderdale, FL, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 91)
- Printers - Jacksonville, FL, 1910-1921 (Box 10, Folder 92)
  1910, 1913, 1915, 1921
- Printers - Mt. Vernon, NY, 1923-1927 (Box 10, Folder 93)
- Printers - Richmond, VA, 1910-1915 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  1910, 1915
- Printers - Burlington, VT, 1922 (Box 10, Folder 95)
- Printers - Salt Lake City, UT, 1910-1919 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  1910, 1914, 1919
- Printers - Parkersburg, WV, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 97)
- Printers - Norfolk, VA, 1915-1926 (Box 10, Folder 98)
  1915, 1917, 1921, 1925, 1926
- Printers - Bowling Green, OH, 1923-1925 (Box 10, Folder 99)
- Printers - Athens, OH, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 100)
- Printers - Fall River, MA, 1907-1924 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  1907, 1909, 1912, 1915-1924
- Printers - Fitchburg, MA, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 102)
- Printers - Haverhill, MA, 1924-1926 (Box 10, Folder 103)
- Printers - Holyoke, MA, 1923-1925 (Box 10, Folder 104)
- Printers - Lowell, MA, 1921-1925 (Box 10, Folder 105)
- Printers - Lynn, MA, 1923-1925 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  1923, 1924, 1925
- Printers - Marlboro-Hudson, MA, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 107)
- Printers - New Bedford, MA, 1923-1927 (Box 10, Folder 108)
- Printers - Victoria, British Columbia, 1924-1927 (Box 10, Folder 109)
- Printers - New York, NY, 1909-1925 (Box 10, Folder 110)
  1909, 1912, 1914, 1917-1921, 1925
- Printers - Cincinnati, OH, 1909-1925 (Box 10, Folder 111)
  1909, 1914, 1918-1923, 1925
- Printers - Akron, OH, 1923-1927 (Box 10, Folder 112)
- Printers - Ashtabula, OH, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 113)
- Printers - Canton, OH, 1923-1926 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Printers - Minneapolis, MN, 1903-1926 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  1903, 1908, 1913, 1918, 1923, 1926
- Printers - Port Hugo, MI, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Printers - Saginaw, MI, 1921-1926 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Printers - Muskegon, MI, 1919 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Printers - Amsterdam, NY, 1923-1927 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Printers - New York, NY, 1907-1927 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  1907, 1909, 1912-1920, 1924-1927
- Printers - St. Paul, MN, 1913-1923 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  1913, 1916, 1919, 1923
- Printers - Vicksburg, MS, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Printers - Rockford, IL, 1923-1924 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Printers - Union Hill, NJ, 1924-1927 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Printers - Buffalo, NY, 1907-1916 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  1907, 1910, 1916
- Printers - Allentown, PA, 1923-1925 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Printers - Altoona, PA, 1923-1927 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  1923, 1924, 1926, 1927
- Printers - Portland, OR, 1917-1924 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  1917, 1918, 1924
- Printers - Bradford, PA, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Printers - Toronto, Ontario, 1922-1928 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  1922, 1925, 1928
- Printers - Oil City, PA, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Printers - Astoria, OR, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Printers - New York, NY (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Printers - Superior, WI, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Printers - Easton, PA, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Printers - Connellsville, PA, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Printers - Butler, PA, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Printers - Houston, TX, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Printers - Erie, PA, 1919-1927 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  1919-1925, 1927
- Printers - Vancouver, Canada, 1923-1927 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Printers - Racine, WI, 1922-1927 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  1922, 1923, 1925, 1927
- Printers - New York, NY, 1920-1924 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Printers - Beaver Falls, PA, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Printers - Portland, OR, 1917-1924 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  1917, 1918, 1921, 1922, 1924
- Printers - Cleveland, OH, 1907-1925 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  1907, 1912, 1917, 1919, 1922-1925
- Printers - Cincinnati, OH, 1905-1924 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  1905, 1910-1915, 1919, 1924
- Printers - Wilkes-Barre, PA, 1921-1926 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  1921, 1923, 1924, 1926
- Printers - Indianapolis, IN (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Printers - Shamokin, PA, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Printers - New York, NY, 1912-1923 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Printers - Portland, OR, 1910-1918 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  1910, 1913, 1918
- Printers - Columbus, OH, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Printers - Dayton, OH, 1915-1925 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  1915, 1918-1921, 1923-1925
- Printers - East Liverpool, OH, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Printers - Pittsburgh, PA, 1909-1928 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  1909, 1913, 1914, 1919-1928
- Printers - Indianapolis, IN, 1913-1926 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  1913, 1915, 1920-1926
- Printers - Globe, AZ, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Printers - Tucson, AZ, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Printers - Evansville, IN, 1923-1926 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Printers - Ft. Wayne, IN, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Printers - Gary, IN, 1924-1925 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  1924, 1925
- Printers - Little Rock, AR, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Printers - Centralia, IL, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Printers - Champaign-Urbana, IL, 1923-1925 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Printers - Cleveland, OH, 1911-1914 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  1911, 1912, 1914
- Printers - Columbus, OH, 1904 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Printers - Tulsa, OK, 1924-1927 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Printers - Portland, OR, 1924-1926 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Printers - Philadelphia, PA, 1906-1923 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  1906, 1910, 1912, 1916, 1918, 1923
- Printers - Baltimore, Mary., 1906-1926 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  1906-1907, 1910, 1913, 1917-1920, 1924-1926
- Printers - Portsmouth, OH, 1924-1926 (Box 11, Folder 58)
- Printers - Chicago, IL, 1904-1926 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  1904, 1909-1920, 1923-1926
- Printers - Ottawa, Ontario, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 60)
- Printers - Perth Amboy, NJ, 1925-1926 (Box 11, Folder 61)
- Printers - New York, NY, 1910-1924 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  1910, 1912, 1918-1921, 1924
- Printers - Plainfield, NJ, 1922-1926 (Box 11, Folder 63)
- Printers - New Castle, PA, 1925-1928 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  1925, 1928
- Printers - Clarksburg, WV, 1925-1927 (Box 11, Folder 65)
- Printers - Franklin, PA, 1923-1926 (Box 11, Folder 66)
- Printers - Erie, PA, 1920-1926 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  1920, 1921, 1922, 1926
- Printers - Harrisburg, PA, 1922-1927 (Box 11, Folder 68)
- Printers - Johnstown, PA, 1923-1926 (Box 11, Folder 69)
- Printers - McKeesport, PA, 1925-1926 (Box 11, Folder 70)
- Printers - London, Ontario, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 71)
- Printers - Hamilton, Canada, 1922-1925 (Box 11, Folder 72)
- Printers - Houston, TX, 1913 (Box 11, Folder 73)
- Printers - Newport, VA, 1924-1926 (Box 11, Folder 74)
- Printers - Temple, TX, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 75)
- Printers - Ft. Worth, TX, 1922-1927 (Box 11, Folder 76)
- Printers - Elizabeth, NJ, 1923-1926 (Box 11, Folder 77)
- Printers - Palo Alto, CA, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 78)
- Printers - Pasadena, CA, 1916-1921 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  1916, 1921
- Printers - Riverside, CA, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 80)
- Printers - Oakland, CA, 1921-1924 (Box 11, Folder 81)
- Printers - Carson City, NV, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 82)
- Printers - Reno, NV, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 83)
- Printers - Camden, NJ, 1921-1923 (Box 11, Folder 84)
- Printers - Los Angeles, CA, 1923-1926 (Box 11, Folder 85)
- Printers - El Centro, CA, 1925-1926 (Box 11, Folder 86)
- Printers - Fresno, CA, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 87)
- Printers - Muncie, IN, 1923-1926 (Box 11, Folder 88)
- Printers - Eureka, CA, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 89)
- Printers - New Orleans, LA, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 90)
- Printers - Spokane, WA, 1910-1922 (Box 11, Folder 91)
  1910, 1915-1922
- Printers - Seattle, WA, 1909-1927 (Box 11, Folder 92)
  1909, 1913, 1917, 1926, 1927
- Printers - Tacoma, WA, 1922-1924 (Box 11, Folder 93)
- Printers - Bluefield, WV, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 94)
- Printers - Charleston, WV, 1923-1925 (Box 11, Folder 95)
- Printers - Hutchinson, KS, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 96)
- Quarry Workers - Graniteville, VT, 1910-1922 (Box 11, Folder 97)
  1910, 1915, 1922
- Quarry Workers - Hardwick, VT, 1903-1906 (Box 11, Folder 98)
- Quarry Workers - Woodbury, VT, 1903-1923 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  1903, 1904, 1906, 1923
- Quarry Workers - Index, WA, 1904 (Box 11, Folder 100)
- Quarry Workers - Berlin, WI, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 101)
- Quarry Workers - Granite Heights, WI, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 102)
- Quarry Workers - Red Granite, WI, 1917 (Box 11, Folder 103)
- Quarry Workers - Westerly, RI, 1922 (Box 11, Folder 104)
- Quarry Workers - Barre, VT, 1905 (Box 11, Folder 105)
- Quarry Workers - Chester, MA, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 106)
- Quarry Workers - Rockport, Mas., 1916-1925 (Box 11, Folder 107)
  1916, 1923, 1925
- Quarry Workers - Milford, MA, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 108)
- Quarry Workers - Quincy, MA, 1905-1923 (Box 11, Folder 109)
- Quarry Workers - Graniteville, MO, 1922-1924 (Box 11, Folder 110)
- Quarry Workers - Concord, NH, 1905-1925 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  1905, 1916, 1919, 1923, 1925
- Quarry Workers - Marlboro, NH, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 112)
- Quarry Workers - Milford, NH, 1922-1924 (Box 11, Folder 113)
- Quarry Workers - Knowles, CA, 1904 (Box 11, Folder 114)
- Quarry Workers - Raymond, CA, 1905-1906 (Box 11, Folder 115)
- Quarry Workers - Stony Creek, CT, 1904-1906 (Box 11, Folder 116)
  1904, 1906
- Quarry Workers - Joliet, IL, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 117)
- Quarry Workers - Frankfort, ME, 1905 (Box 11, Folder 118)
- Quarry Workers - Hallowell, ME, 1928 (Box 11, Folder 119)
- Quarry Workers - High Island, ME, 1905 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Quarry Workers - Hurricane, ME, 1905 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Quarry Workers - North Jay, ME, 1904 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Quarry Workers - North Sullivan, ME, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Quarry Workers - Hall Quarry, ME, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Quarry Workers - Hallowell, ME, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Quarry Workers - Stonington, ME, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Quarry Workers - Fitchburg, MA, 1922-1924 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Lumpers, Boxers and Derrickmen - Brattleboro, VT, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Lumpers, Boxers and Derrickmen - Barre, VT, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Quarry Workers - Milford, MA, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Radio Operators - National, 1919-1923 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  1919, 1921, 1922, 1923
- Restaurants - Salt Lake City, UT (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Riggers and Machinery Movers - Philadelphia, PA, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Rod Workers - Washington D.C., 1923 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Roofers - Newark, NJ, 1916-1925 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  1916, 1924, 1925
- Roofers - Rochester, NY, 1920-1925 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Roofers (composition) - New York, NY, 1914-1923 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  1914, 1921, 1923
- Slate, Tile, and Asbestos Roofers - Chicago, IL, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Roofers (composition) - Cincinnati, OH, 1915-1918 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Slate and Tile Roofers - NJ, 1919-1920 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Roofers - Perth Amboy, NJ, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Roofers - Buffalo, NY, 1913-1925 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  1913, 1925
- Roofers - New York, NY, 1916-1924 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  1916, 1918, 1924
- Roofers (composition) - Rochester, NY, 1914-1919 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  1914, 1917, 1919
- Roofers - Cincinnati, OH, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Slate and Tile Roofers - Cleveland, OH, 1914 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Roofers - Pittsburgh, PA, 1915-1925 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  1915, 1916, 1923, 1924, 1925
- Roofers - Philadelphia, PA, 1914-1925 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  1914, 1916, 1920, 1925
- Roofers - Youngstown, OH, 1921-1926 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Roofers - Dayton, OH, 1920-1923 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Roofers - Cleveland, OH, 1923-1925 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Roofers - Boston, MA (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Roofers - Des Moines, IA, 1924 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Roofers (composition) - Pittsburgh, PA, 1915-1925 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  1915, 1916, 1918, 1919, 1923, 1924, 1925
- Roofers - Scranton, PA, 1915-1924 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  1915, 1916, 1917, 1924
- Roofers (composition) - Seattle, WA, 1914-1916 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  1914, 1916
- Roofers (composition) - Milwaukee, WI, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Slate and Tile Roofers - Cincinnati, OH, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Roofers - Norfolk, VA, 1925 (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Slate, Tile, and Asbestos Roofers - Chicago, IL, 1915-1918 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  1915, 1917, 1918
- Roofers (composition) - Cleveland, OH, 1915-1918 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  1915, 1916, 1917, 1918
- Roofers (composition) - Davenport, IA, 1919 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Roofers - Ft. Lauderdale, FL, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Roofers - West Palm Beach, FL, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Roofers (composition) - Boston, MA, 1914-1923 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  1914, 1917, 1919, 1923
- Roofers - Lynn, MA, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Roofers (composition) - Newark, NJ, 1916-1919 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Slate and Tile Roofers - St. Louis, MO, 1906-1922 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  1906, 1922
- Roofers (composition) - Kansas City, MO, 1914-1918 (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Rubber Workers - Hudson, MA, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Sailmakers - Philadelphia, PA, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Scale Workers - Rutland, VT, 1926 (Box 12, Folder 53)
- Rubber Workers - Providence, RI, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 54)
- Seamen - National, 1904-1928 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  1904, 1905, 1906, 1921, 1922, 1927, 1928
- Sheet Metal Workers - New York, NY, 1913-1925 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  1913, 1915, 1918, 1919, 1923, 1924, 1925
- Sailors - Great Lakes, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 57)
- Lake Seamen - National, 1907-1927 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  1907, 1927
- Firemen, Seamen and Water Tenders - National, 1922 (Box 12, Folder 59)
- Unlicensed Deck and Engine Dept. Crews - New York, NY, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 60)
- Ship Caulkers - Portland, OR, 1918 (Box 12, Folder 61)
- Shipwrights - Chicago, IL, 1898 (Box 12, Folder 62)
- Shipwrights - Seattle, WA, 1917 (Box 12, Folder 63)
- Shingle Weavers - Kalama, WA, 1928 (Box 12, Folder 64)
- Shingle Workers - Hogwiam, WA, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 65)
- Seamen - Providence, RI (Box 12, Folder 66)
- Stewards - National, 1919-1923 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  1919, 1922, 1923
- Stewards - Great Lakes, 1906 (Box 12, Folder 68)
- Marine Cooks and Stewards - Great Lakes, 1906 (Box 12, Folder 69)
- Marine Cooks and Stewards - Chicago, IL, 1912-1927 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  1912, 1927
- Marine Cooks and Stewards - Atlantic Coast, 1905-1927 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  1905, 1927
- Marine Firemen, Oilers and Water Tenders - Great Lakes, 1901-1923 (Box 12, Folder 72)
  1901, 1902, 1903, 1905, 1923
- Masters, Mates and Pilots - Balboa, Canal Zone, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 73)
- Masters, Mates and Deck Officers - National, 1924-1926 (Box 12, Folder 74)
  1924, 1925, 1926
- Masters, Mates and Pilots - Norfolk, VA, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 75)
- Masters, Mates and Pilots - Baltimore, Mary., 1923 (Box 12, Folder 76)
- Masters, Mates and Pilots - Milwaukee, WI, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 77)